(Leonard:)If you're not happy,
just let Kripke have the office.
Wait, and let him win?
Do I look crazy to you?
(Sheldon:)We're trying to think down here,
you geode-loving feldspar jockeys!
(Sheldon:)And you,
the notes are C, D, E, G and A.
(Sheldon:)You pick one
or I'm chopping down that tree!
- How's that?
- Little higher on the right.
(Sheldon:)- Now?
- Little more.
(Amy:)No. That's got it.
Yeah, okay. That's good.
- I'll let you in on a little secret.
- Mm.
(Amy:)Originally, we were painted nude.
But I had him add clothes because
it was an unnecessary challenge...
(Amy:)...to our heterosexuality.
(Penny:)Yeah, good call.
If you change your mind, all it
would take is some warm soapy water...
(Amy:)...and a couple of sponges.
- You're talking about the painting, right?
- Sure.
(Sheldon:)Help! Somebody, help!
(Leonard:)What happened?
l was trying to see what was in here
and my head got stuck.
(Leonard:)Why would you do that?
(Sheldon:)It's called scientific curiosity.
(Sheldon:)Now go get butter.
Okay, okay. Hang in there.
I'll be right back.